urbanize.la 2019-12-06

# Privacy Policy | Urbanize LA

The following Privacy Policy summarizes the various ways that Urbanize Media LLC (“we”, “us”, “our” or “Urbanize LA”) uses the information you provide while accessing or using [http://www.urbanize.la](http://www.urbanize.la/) (the “Website”). It is our goal to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy.

Please read this Privacy Policy and the Website Terms of Use carefully. Your accessing or use of any aspect of the Website will constitute your agreement to this Privacy Policy and the Website Terms of Use. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy or the Website Terms of Use, you may do not use the Website. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including without limitation offline and on sites linked to from the Website.

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time. Continued access of the Website by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

**The Type of Information the We May Collect**

**1\. Personally Identifiable Information.**

The Website may request information about you to establish an online account. Such information may include personally identifiable information, such as your actual name, email, address, telephone number, and billing information. Optional information such as your age or gender may also be requested. You may at any time update your personal information by logging into your account.

**2\. Information About Site Visits.**

While you may visit our Website without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information, the Website may gather statistical information to understand our users’ use of the Website. This information may include the number of visitors, frequency of visits and which areas of the Website are most popular. This information is used in aggregate form to make continual improvements to our Website.

**3\. Domain Information.**

This Website may also collect certain information to become more acquainted with customers who visit the Website. It helps us understand how the Website is being used, so that we may make it even more beneficial to our users. This information may include the date, time, and pages you access, the Internet Service Provider (ISP) and the Internet Protocol (IP) address by which you are accessing the Internet and the Internet address from where you linked to our Website.

**How the Website Uses Information Provided by You**

We also allow access to our database by third parties that provide us with services, such as technical maintenance or forums software, but only for the purpose of and to the extent necessary to provide those services. There are also times when you provide information about yourself to us in areas of the site that may be managed or participated in by third parties. In such cases, the information may be used by us and by such third parties, each pursuant to its own policies. We may also provide your information to our advertisers, so that they can serve ads to you that meet your needs or match your interests. While we will seek to require such third parties to follow appropriate privacy policies and will not authorize them to use this information except for the express purpose for which it is provided, we bear no responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties. There may also be occasion when we are legally required to provide access to our database in order to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings. In those instances, the information is provided only for that purpose.

In addition, we reserve the right to use the information we collect about your computer, which may at times be able to identify you, for any lawful business purpose, including without limitation to help diagnose problems with our servers, to gather broad demographic information, and to otherwise administer our Website. We reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.

In addition, as our business changes, we may buy or sell various assets. In the event all or a portion of the assets owned or controlled by us, our parent or any subsidiary or affiliated entity are sold, assigned, transferred or acquired by another company, the information from and/or about our Website users may be among the transferred assets.

**Cookies**

We may use cookies to control the display of ads, to track usage patterns on the site, to deliver editorial content, and to record registration and personalization information. For example, if you register on any part of the Website and are given the option to save your username and password on your computer, we can provide this convenience to you by placing a cookie on your computer. Our cookies may contain personally identifiable information and such cookies may be shared with our affiliates and other companies.

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers.

We may also use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the Website. These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and we disclaim all liability in connection therewith.

We may participate in affiliate marketing and allow affiliate links to be encoded on some of our pages. This means that we may earn a commission when you click on or make purchases via affiliate links and affiliate partners may use cookies to understand your use of the services.

If you don't want any cookies, your web browser likely includes an option that allows you to not accept them. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of the Website may not function properly.

**Safeguarding Children**

This Website is not directed towards children under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information or use our public discussion areas, forums and chats. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardian(s) before transacting on this site.

If your children disclose information about themselves in publicly accessible areas of the Website, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. Accordingly, you should tell them not to do so.

If you're worried about your children's activities or their privacy on our Website, we encourage you to contact us.

**Contacting Us**

For inquiries concerning this Privacy Policy or our Website Terms of Use you may contact us at [info@urbanize.la](mailto:info@urbanize.la).

Last Updated August 30, 2019
